Guide to the Cornell United Religious Work records, 1869-1972,
Cornell United Religious Work records
- Series I
  - Hidden Valley, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Freshman camp Housing, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Sourcebook Hidden Valley, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Freshman camp, 1955-56 (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Co-ed camp counselors, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Freshman Camp business, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Camps Home, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Freshman Camp General, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Freshman Camp Questionnaires, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Freshman camp registration, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - Men's camp counselors, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - Bill Greenwalt Freshman Camp Source Book, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - Women's source book, 1954 (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - Freshman camp policy board, 1953-55 (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - Reports and Evaluations Women's Freshman Camp, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 51)
  - Womens freshman camp, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - Men's camp, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - Camps, 1953 (Box 23, Folder 54)
  - Men's camp, 1952 (Box 23, Folder 55)
  - Freshman camp, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 56)
  - Men's camps, 1951 (Box 23, Folder 57)
  - Men's camp, 1950 (Box 23, Folder 58)
  - Men's camp, 1949 (Box 23, Folder 59)
  - Men's camp, 1948 (Box 23, Folder 60)
  - Men's fresh camp, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 61)
  - Men's freshman camp, 1946 (Box 23, Folder 62)
  - Freshman camps worship and song sheets, 1950s (Box 23, Folder 63)
  - Freshman camp policy board historical, 1950 (Box 23, Folder 64)
  - Freshman Camp history, 1951 (Box 23, Folder 65)
  - Freshman Camp Worship service, 1934 (Box 23, Folder 66)
  - SVM Athens conference, 1959-60 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Student Volunteer Movements, 1955-56 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - SVM follow up 2nd semester, 1955-56 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - SVM study groups for conference, Christmas, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - SVM conference preparation, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - SVM questions returned Christmas Conference, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - SVM general interpretation material, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - SVM lists of overseas Christmas, 1955-56 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - SVM visitor MA Thomas, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - USCC correspondence, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - United student Christmas council, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - World's Student Christian Federation Interpretive, 1949 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - World student day of prayer, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Student day of prayer, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - World student day of prayer past materials, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - World student service fund, 1950 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - World University Service, 1955 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - YM-YW, 1953-54 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - YMCA-YWCA, 1954-55 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - NSA NSCY, 1953 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - National YMCA and YWCA, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - National YW and YWCA, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - YMCA, 1956-57 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - One world club, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Manual of operations and reports, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - One world club finance and budgets, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Speaker file, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - One world club, 1951-52 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - One World club, 1952-53 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - One World club, 1953-54 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - One World club, 1954-55 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - One world club, 1955-56 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence previous to 1956, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence to 1956, 1956 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - One World club, 1956-57 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - One World club: spring seminar, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - One world club, 1957-58 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence, 1958-59 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - One world club correspondence, 1959-60 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - One world club, 1960-61 (Box 24, Folder 40)
  - Biographics One world, 1960-61 (Box 24, Folder 41)
  - One world club treasurer's report, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 42)
  - One world club questionnaire, 1961 (Box 24, Folder 43)
  - One World club, 1961-62 (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - One World club, 1962-63 (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - One World club correspondence, 1962-63 (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - OWC, 1962-63 (Box 24, Folder 47)
  - One World club correspondence, 1963-64 (Box 24, Folder 48)
  - One world club, 1964-65 (Box 24, Folder 49)
  - One World club, 1964-65 (Box 24, Folder 50)
  - One World club, 1965-66 (Box 24, Folder 51)
  - Committee Minutes, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 52)
  - One world club membership cards (Box 24, Folder 53)
  - One world club membership cards (Box 24, Folder 54)
  - Barnes Library Books, 1940s (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Student Cabinet, 1960-70 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - McKee, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Swami Ranganathanada, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Mitchell Musician in residence, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Burtt Phil-in-residence, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Birenbaum Philosopher in residence, 1967-68 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Kallen Philosopher in residence, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Freshman CURW Orientation, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Ithaca tutorial, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Dialogue, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Organization CURW, 1969-71 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - CURW job description, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Annual Report, 1962-64 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - CURW conference, 1963 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Conference Centers, 1957-63 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - 12.01 CURW, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - 12.0 CURW general and calendar, 1958-59 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - 12.2 CURW, 1959-60 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - 12.1 CURW, 1958-59 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - 12.3 CURW, 1960-61 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - 12.4 CURW, 1961-62 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - 12.5 CURW, 1962-63 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - 12.6 CRUR, 1963-64 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - 12.7 CURW, 1964-65 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - 12.13 CURW: board minutes, 1960-67 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - 12.15 CURW: staff minutes, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Beyond the Ivory Tower, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Press Coverage, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Commercial Movement, 1960-62 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Ecumenism and CURW, 1961-62 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Lectures and Responses "Ecumenism", 1961-62 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - A Correspondence, 1962-63 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Arts committee, 1963 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Africa, 1961-63 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - B correspondence, 1960-63 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - C correspondence, 1960-63 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Denominational Band, 1960-93 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Dialogue, 1960-63 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Ecumenical, 1961-63 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Education area, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Freshman Area, 1961-63 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - F correspondence, 1960-63 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - I correspondence, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - International Area, 1962-63 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - J correspondence, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - K correspondence, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Program religion at Cornell, 1959-61 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Foreign students general, 1956 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Cornell in China, 1942 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Past CURW programs for foreign students report on cosmopolitan club, 1951-56 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - International night by freshman club, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - International student spring conference, 1955 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - International department, 1956-57 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - International Relations clubs, 1957-59 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Interoc Including newsletter, 1958-59 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - International Area, 1959-60 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - International area, 1958-59 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Foreign student list, 1959-61 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - International center committee, 1957-59 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - International orientation, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Leadership training program, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - L correspondence, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Memoirs, 1961-63 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - N correspondence, 1961-62 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - P correspondence, 1961-62 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Protestant council, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Pre Theological, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - R correspondence, 1961-62 (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Scholarships, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - Sermons, 1962-63 (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - S correspondence, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 40)
  - Summer work camps, 1961-622 (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - Student Christian movement, 1961-64 (Box 26, Folder 42)
  - Student code, 1961-62 (Box 26, Folder 43)
  - Summer jobs abroad, 1961-63 (Box 26, Folder 44)
  - SCM conference correspondence, 1957-58 (Box 26, Folder 45)
  - New York SCM, Historical, Purpose and relationships, 1948 (Box 26, Folder 46)
  - New York state SCM, 1953-55 (Box 26, Folder 47)
  - New York state SCM, 1955-56 (Box 26, Folder 48)
  - Student Christian movement, 1958 (Box 26, Folder 49)
  - Tillich, Paul, 1961-62 (Box 26, Folder 50)
  - Tillich, 1961-62 (Box 26, Folder 51)
  - Thorp Lectures, 1960-62 (Box 26, Folder 52)
  - U correspondence, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 53)
  - Union theological seminary, 1961-62 (Box 26, Folder 54)
  - VIPs, 1958-60 (Box 26, Folder 55)
  - V correspondence, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 56)
  - W correspondence, 1961-62 (Box 26, Folder 57)
  - Y correspondence, 1961-63 (Box 26, Folder 58)
  - Washington seminar, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 59)
  - Washington seminar, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 60)
  - September, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 61)
  - October, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 62)
  - November, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 63)
  - December, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 64)
  - January, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 65)
  - February, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 66)
  - March, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 67)
  - April, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 68)
  - May, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 69)
  - World religions, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 70)
  - Constitution of the Christian Association of Cornell University, 1869-95 (Box 27, Volume 1)
  - CURW Board, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - CURW board, 1977-80 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Cornell chaplaincy, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - University Ministries Brochures, 1990-96 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Conferences, various, 1965-87 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Sage speaker lists, 1963-85 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Archives, 1950-65 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Centennial, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Conferences, 1987-90 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Martin Luther King JR, 1992-99 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Sage Misc Series, 1975-99 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Words/music, 1968-95 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Welcome to Sage Chapel, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Student preacher award, 1986-93 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Cornell Conference on religion, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Wood lectures, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Baccalaureate Service, 1981-95 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Common's Coffee House Poster, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Memorial Service, 1964-69 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Sage funding, 1980-81 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Invitations to Sage, 1985-95 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - ATH poster, No date (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - CURW sponsored readings, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - CURW covenant, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Festival for religious arts, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Compendia of religious perspectives in Cornell, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Courses/religious studies, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Orientation activities, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Sage Develop brochures, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Sage Rose report, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - CURW info, 1988-99 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Newsletter of CURW Service, Area, various reports on Activities, 1950s-1960s (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Miscellaneous papers and correspondence, 1960s (Box 28, Folder 33)
    Includes Senate Study of the Report of the Commission on Self-Governance
  - Miscellaneous papers and correspondence, 1970s (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Miscellaneous papers and correspondence, 1980s (Box 28, Folder 35)
    Includes information on the Leonardo Da Vinci Society
  - Files regarding the direction, structure and tasks of CURW, 1960s-1970s (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - Files regarding religious affiliation and preference of Cornell students, 1950s-1960s (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - Rite of Passage incoming freshman matriculation ceremony, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - Miscellaneous brochures, 1960s-1970s (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Art Exhibit, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Crucifixion Statue, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Survey, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - International weekends, 1950-60 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Binghamton, 1978-81 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Orientation, 1972-77 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Orientation, 1968-71 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Orientation, 1964-67 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Orientation Freshman, 1961 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Marriage series, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Sign of Jonah, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - James Baldwin, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - The story of the Christian church, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - John R Mott, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - History of University, 1941 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Mott, John R Centennial, 1966 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Mott Notes, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - John Mott Centennial, 1965 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - General correspondence, 1954-55 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Inter Faith Policies, 1948-49 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - File copy staff minutes, 1965-66 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Board of council minutes, 1949-50 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Board of council minutes, 1948-49 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Manual of CURW, 1959 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Student Board, 1954 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - CURW general, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - CURW budget and expenses, 1954-58 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - CURW budget student board, 1957-58 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - CURW general, 1956-57 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - CURW, 1956 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Student board, 1961 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - CURW, 1955-56 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - CURW, 1928 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - CURW, 1958 (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - CURW, 1960-62 (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - Planning conference, 1953-54 (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - Ex-comm agendas, 1954-55 (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - Personnel (lists) student board, 1954-60 (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - Functions, 1952-55 (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - CURW staff meetings, 1953-59 (Box 29, Folder 40)
  - Orientation, 1971-80 (Box 29, Folder 41)
  - Of historical value, 1928-51 (Box 29, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence and campus conference information, 1941-1952 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Notes and clippings on the student board, 1951-9152 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Chaplain Retreat, 1957 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence about CUCA/CURW, as well as freshman survey results and meeting minutes, 1920-1930 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - "International Speaking", 1961-1965 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - "A Study of Cornell United Religious Work", by Mary Harris, 1953 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Calendars, 1951-1962 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Civil Rights Newsletter, CURW University Relationship, and conference materials, 1952, 1957, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Energy conservation and heating, 1973-1979 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Sale of CURW residence letter, June 26, 1952 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Students attending conferences, 1948-1953 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - SCM, Chaplains, etc., 1959 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - News Releases, 1961-1963 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Constitution of CACU, correspondence, and finances, 1921-1924 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Board of Control documents, 1933-1934, 1960 (Box 33, Folder 15-16)
  - News, Board of Control, 1934-1935 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Staff Theological views, 1955-1956 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Account book, 1988-1995 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - CURW Brochure in process, 1962-1964 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - General CURW information, 1950s (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Student board documents, 1950s (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Listening to the Poor (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - CURW and YWCA documents and correspondence, 1940s-1950s (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - CURW student board accounts, 1957-1958 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Budgets, conferences, lectures, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - CURW International, including photograph of Deane Malott, Nathaniel Pierce, and John Summerskill, 1950s (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Anabel Taylor Hall building, equipment, furnishings, 1971-1974 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - History and University relations, 1950s-1960s (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Meeting minutes, conference information, 1950s (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - CURW information, 1930s (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Staff and board memos, 1960-1962 (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - Noncredit courses, Fall, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - Noncredit courses, Fall, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - CURW General: Associate director for studies job description and evaluation, 1963-1966 (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - Directors and Staff clippings, 1968-1969 (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - CURW General: Job description for John Lee Smith's secretary (Box 33, Folder 37)
  - CURW General: Report to CURW board from associate director for studies, 1968-1969 (Box 33, Folder 38)
  - Seminary interns, John "Jack" Costello, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 39)
  - Campus conference on education, 1954 (Box 33, Folder 40)
  - Danforth Foundation program in outline, 1956 (Box 33, Folder 41)
  - Noncredit courses, 1960-1963 (Box 33, Folder 42-44)
  - Memorial service for Ed Christie: Rabbi's remarks, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 45)
  - Criteria for establishing priorities in selecting projects, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 46)
  - Silent march of mourning: Konvitz, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 47)
  - Research commission letter and questionnaire to incoming freshman sampling, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 48)
  - Counseling service report, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 49)
  - Toward clarification (nature and task of CURW), 1962-1963 (Box 33, Folder 50)
  - Memo regarding constituent group support, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 51)
  - Proposal for restructuring boards, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 52)
  - Worship commission report, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 53)
  - Back copies of "The Whale", 1963-1964 (Box 33, Folder 54)
  - Jaquith statement regarding associate directos, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 55)
  - "When Hopes are Shattered" sermon by Jaquith at time of Kennedy's assassination, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 56)
  - Proposal for restructuring board, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 57)
  - Issues and alternatives in reorganization proposals, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 58)
  - Frosh Club documents, 1949-1954 (Box 33, Folder 59)
  - Idiodyssey, 1952 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - CURW evaluation, 1954-1955 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Programing, 1954 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Campus conference on religion, 1954 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Show material, 1954 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - "Campus Life", ca 1950s (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Washington trip, 1952-1957 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - International projects, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Project to Greece, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Washington seminar, 1960 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Campus relations committee, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Past international conferences, 1951-1952 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Foreign Student Orientation Camp: Policy Board, 1954 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - foreign Student Conference, 1955 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Tenth Annual International Orientation Conference, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - International weekend, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - International weekend, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - International weekend, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Treasurer's Records: women's cabinet and activities committee, 1939-1945 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Social Committee, 1940-1946 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Sororities, 1949 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Women's Activities: off-campus lunch club, 1944 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Willard Straight committee and documents, 1939-1943 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Speakers (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Missionaries at Cornell, 1944, 1949 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Rural Fellowship Team, 1948-1949 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Women's Activities Committee, 1947-1948 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Women's Self Government Association, 1939-1950 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - CURW Survey, 1951 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Report of CURW Committee on Discrimination in Cornell Admissions Policy, 1952 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Interfaith Roundtable, 1950-1951 (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - CURW Planning Conferences, 1949-1952 (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - Retreats, 1953-1954 (Box 34, Folder 33)
  - SCM,Cornell, 1944-1952 (Box 34, Folder 34)
  - SCM, Cornell: Purpose and Relationships, 1943-1951 (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - Inter-Protestant Council (SCM Cornell), 1953-1954 (Box 34, Folder 36)
  - Inter-Protestant Council (SCM Cornell), 1954-1955 (Box 34, Folder 37)
  - Staff Minutes, 1952-1953 (Box 34, Folder 38)
  - Board of Control, 1952-1953 (Box 34, Folder 39)
  - Public Affairs Department, 1949-1950 (Box 34, Folder 40)
  - Public Affairs Department, 1950-1951 (Box 34, Folder 41)
  - Freshman Department, 1952-1953 (Box 34, Folder 42)
  - Campus Life (upper class), 1952-1953 (Box 34, Folder 43)
  - Campus Life (upper class), 1950-1951 (Box 34, Folder 44)
  - Campus Life (upper class), 1949-1951 (Box 34, Folder 45)
  - International Department of CURW (historical), 1951-1953 (Box 34, Folder 46)
  - International Student Spring Conference, 1953 (Box 34, Folder 47)
  - Campus Conference on Religion, 1950-1952 (Box 34, Folder 48-50)
  - Calendars, 1955-1961 (Box 34, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence, 1953-1956 (Box 34, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence, 1956-1960 (Box 34, Folder 53)
  - CURW Vocations Conference, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 54)
  - Leadership Lists, 1954-1955 (Box 34, Folder 55)
  - Protestant Staff Retreat, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 56)
  - Foundation Report to CURW Council, 1958-1959 (Box 34, Folder 57)
  - Protestant staff, 1959 (Box 34, Folder 58)
  - Personnel: Historical, 1945-1950 (Box 34, Folder 59)
  - Personnel: Policies (Box 34, Folder 60)
  - Policy boards (Box 34, Folder 61)
  - Publicity material: past year, 1955 (Box 34, Folder 62)
  - Religious groups, 1953-1955 (Box 34, Folder 63)
  - Religious groups: General material (Box 34, Folder 64)
  - Scheduling, 1955 (Box 34, Folder 65)
  - Papers presented for staff discussions, ca 1950s (Box 34, Folder 66)
  - Staff survey on theology, 1955 (Box 34, Folder 67)
  - Statement by "olds", 1957 (Box 34, Folder 68)
  - CURW memorandum, campus religious group pamphlets, 1950s-1960s (Box 34, Folder 69)
  - The National Conference of Christians and Jews (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Report of Religious Education Committee, 1952-1955 (Box 35, Folder 2-3)
  - Student Council Leadership conferences, 1949-1950 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - National Association of College and University Chaplains, 1952-1953 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Bailey Hall show, 1951 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Public Relations Department and publicity, 1953-1954 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - May centennial program participants, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Schemann, Alexander correspondence, 1960 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Barnes, Roswell correspondence, 1960 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Ecumenical movement, 1961 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Student board meeting minutes, publicity, 1960s (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Church boards, regarding Anabel Taylor Hall, 1947-1949 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Religious Vocations Group, 1960 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Students in Government seminar (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Compendia, 1960 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Spring and fall conference information, 1956-1960 (Box 35, Folder 17-23)
  - Biographical: Speakers, 1950s-1960s (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Ithaca Map, ca. 1950s (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Maps of freshman camp, 1955 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Hand drawn road maps (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Routes to miscellaneous conference centers (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - Peace Corps, 1963 (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Olatunji concert, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Voter registration project, 1964 (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - Peace Corps religious questionnaire, 1963 (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - Washington Seminar, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - Education area, 1960-1961 (Box 35, Folder 34)
  - International Area, 1960-1961 (Box 35, Folder 35)
  - Presbyterian Westminster Foundation, 1962 (Box 35, Folder 36)
  - African Seminar, 1961-1962 (Box 35, Folder 37)
  - Staff meeting, 1961-1962 (Box 35, Folder 38)
  - Protestant staff, 1960-1961 (Box 35, Folder 39)